Sol M. Linowitz Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Classified, 1962-1982 (Box CL 1-CL 3)
  - Government Service (Box CL 1)
    - Middle East Peace Negotiations
      - Palestinians, 1980 (Container 130)
      - Plenary statement, 1980, undated (Container 131)
      - Press conferences and interviews, 1980 (Container 131)
      - Reports to the president, 1979-1981, undated (Container 131), (2 folders)
      - Speeches and writings
        - Speech file, 1980 (Container 133)
      - Travel and meeting itineraries, 1980 (Container 136)
  - General Office File
    - Part A
      - Government
        - Advisory Committee on International Organizations, State Department
          - Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Container 207)
          - Meetings, 1962-1966 (Container 207)
          - Miscellany, 1963-1964, undated (Container 208)
          - Reports
            - “Financial Management of the United Nations System”
              - Correspondence, 1963, undated (Container 208)
              - United States budgetary procedures and policies, 1963, undated (Container 208)
            - “Staffing International Organizations” (Box CL 3)
              - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Container 209)
              - Miscellany, undated (Container 209)
              - Report
                - Text, 1963, undated (Container 210)
            - “Technical Cooperation Programs of the United Nations System”
              - Correspondence, 1963 (Container 210)
              - Miscellany, 1963 (Container 210)
              - Report, undated (Container 210)
          - Subcommittee on Peacekeeping Operations
            - Article 19 of the U.N. Charter, 1963-1964 (Container 210)
            - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Container 211)
            - Miscellany, 1962-1963 (Container 211)
        - International Development
          - National Committee for International Development
            - Meetings, 1966 (Container 217)
        - President's General Advisory Committee on Foreign Assistance Programs
          - General correspondence, 1965 (Containers 219-220)
          - Meetings, 1965-1966 (Container 220), (3 folders)
          - Memoranda and reports, 1965-1966 (Container 221)
          - Reports from foreign countries, 1965-1966 (Container 222)
    - Part B
      - Travel file
        - 1982
          - Jan. Egypt/Israel
            - Egypt (Container 515)
  - Speeches and writings
    - Part B
      - By Linowitz
        - Chronological File
          - 1967, Dec. 12 (Container 588)
          - 1968, Feb. 9 (Container 589)
- Oversize, 1945-1993 (Box OV 1-OV 16)
  Broadsides, photographs, a photocopy of a drawing, and scrapbooks.
  - Government Service (Box OV 1)
    - Panama Canal treaties
      - General correspondence, map, 1977 (Container 117)
    - Middle East peace negotiations
      - Israeli settlements in occupied territories, map, undated (Container 129)
  - General Office File
    - Part A
      - Rank Xerox
        - Rank Organisation
          - Miscellany, broadside, 1959-1960 (Container 256)
    - Part B
      - American Red Cross
        - Correspondence, photographs, 1970-1972 (Container 308-309)
      - Bohemian Club, San Francisco, Calif.
        - Miscellany, broadsides, 1971-1990 (Container 313)
      - Travel file
        - 1978, Mar., Africa/Middle East
          - Arrangements, broadside, 1978 (Container 513)
  - Miscellany
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, photocopy of drawing by Onassis, undated (Container 635)
    - Photographs
      - White House
        - Johnson, Lyndon B., administration, 1967-1969 (Container 635)
    - Scrapbooks (Box OV 2)
      - Set II
        - China, 1979 (Container 638)
        - Japan, undated (Container 638) (Box OV 3)
        - Mexico, 1965 (Container 638) (Box OV 4)
        - Miscellany (Box OV 5)
          - 1945-1993 (Container 638)
          - 1951-1966 (Container 638) (Box OV 6)
        - Organization of American States (Box OV 7)
          - Vol. 1, 1966-1969 (Container 638)
          - Vol. 2, 1967, Apr.-Aug. (Container 638) (Box OV 8)
          - Vol. 3, 1967, Aug.-Nov. (Container 638) (Box OV 9)
          - Vol. 4, 1967, Nov.-Dec. (Container 638) (Box OV 10)
          - Vol. 5, 1967, Dec.-1968, Feb. (Container 638) (Box OV 11)
          - Vol. 6, 1968, Feb.-June (Container 638) (Box OV 12)
          - Vol. 7, 1968, July-1969, Apr. (Container 638) (Box OV 13)
          - Vol. 8, foreign language, 1967-1968 (Container 638) (Box OV 14)
        - Panama Canal, 1977-1978 (Box OV 15)
          - Vol. 1 (Container 638)
          - Vol. 2 (Container 638) (Box OV 16)